"超鸡棒"火鸡狂欢节暨火鸡快跑活动
感恩节当天
翻译：小布拿拿      Tiogy      红豆包      斯人
这就是那些鸡吗
Those are the birds?
它们为啥要发出那种声音
W-why they making that noise?
翻译&校对&总监：Iz
鬼知道
Hell if I know.
它们已经那样叫唤了
They've been screeching that way
八小时了
for the last eight hours.
它们是从哪儿来的
Where are they from?
一个可怕的破农场
They came from a horrible crappy farm, okay?
后期：斯人     时间轴：深夏桃子
■
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
赶紧签字
Just sign the form.
我想离开这里
I want to get out of here.
那些鸡让我毛骨悚然
Those birds give me the creeps.
得了吧  能怎么样
Come on, how bad can it be?
就是一群可爱的小火鸡
They're just a bunch of cute little birdies.
它们也许只是饿了
They're probably hungry.
是啊  来  伙计
Yeah. Here you go, buddy.
想吃饼干吗
You want some pretzel?
我的手
My hand!
你的纤纤细手啊
Not your beautiful hand!
火鸡黎明
[影射美国恐怖电影《活死人黎明》"Dawn of the Dead"]
当心了  大家
Look out, everyone.
前方有急弯
Dangerous curves ahead.
*火鸡快跑  热辣劲爆*
*Turkey trot, looking hot*
*你们喜欢我的裤子吗*
*Do you like these pants I got? *
喜欢吗
Do you?
鲍勃  你喜欢吗
Bob, do you?
是的  我喜欢
Yes. I like them.
很好看  我喜欢
They're... fine. I love them.
等等  等等  我把腰带系上
Wait, wait. Let me put my belt on.
你确定你带的水够喝吗  老妈
You sure you got enough water, Mom?
我得不断补充水分嘛
Hey, you got to stay hydrated.
而且你看这瓶子多小啊
Plus, look how little they are!
好迷你
So tiny.
我已经等不及了
Can't wait to get out there.
五百只活火鸡和人一起跑步
500 live turkeys running with us.
和奔牛节差不多  但又萌又无害
It's gonna be like the running of the bulls but cute and safe!
而且游乐设施全五折  但欢乐不打折
And we'll be on the half-price rides having full-priced fun.
老爸  你还在因为我们
Dad, are you still mad at us
去参加狂欢节生气吗
for going to the festval?
生气  不  我高兴得很
Mad!? No, I'm thrilled!
可你那天貌似就有点生气
Because you were kind of mad the other day.
什么  不  我没有
What? No, I was... I wasn't.
太好了  和鸡赛跑  坐游乐设施
Oh, right! 'Cause that's what Thanksgiving is for,
感恩节做这个简直太有意义了
running around with a bunch of birds and going on rides!
好吧  去吧  但给我听着
Well, fine! Go! But you know what?
我不会做晚饭的
I'm not making dinner!
他还满能接受这事的嘛
He's taking this pretty well.
不  你才在哭
No, you're crying!
我只是很平静地表示
I just calmly said that if you all go
如果你们都要去参加费舍奥德那破狂欢节
to Fischoeder's dumb festival instead of spending
而放弃在家过节  我就不做饭了
the day here, I will not be making dinner.
老鲍勃要放一天假了
Day off for old Bob.
-没什么大不了的  -没什么大不了的
- No big deal. - No big deal!
火鸡滴油管在抽屉里
The turkey baster is in the drawer,
也许正乐得派不上用场  和我一样
probably pretty happy not to work, and so am I.
好吧  走了  可别错过了
All right, come on. Don't want to be late
"超鸡棒"火鸡狂欢节和火鸡快跑活动
for the Turk-tacular Turkey Town Festival and Turkey Trot.
好吧  你们都去狂欢吧
Fine! You all go have a Turk-tacular time.
要不我们带点中国菜回来
So, we'll bring home some Chinese food?
好啊  管它什么感恩节
Yup! Or whatever you want for Thanks...
你们大可以想吃啥就带啥
I mean, regular dinner.
好吧  我们不在你可别把家变成妓院
Okay, don't start a brothel while we're gone.
开玩笑的  你可以的
Just kidding, you can.
也不要用沙发垫子搭堡垒
And no making a fort out of the couch cushions.
开玩笑的  你可以的
Just kiddig, you can.
但不要把那堡垒变成妓院
But don't turn that fort into a brothel.
开玩笑的  你可以的
Just kidding, you can.
天哪
Oh, my God, just...
我是说  虽然不合法  但
I mean, it's illegal, but...
知道了  赶紧走吧
I know. Just leave.
好一双腿
Nice stems!
谢谢
Thank you.
为了遮静脉曲张的血管  我穿了长筒袜
I'm wearing hose to compress my varicose veins.
泰迪  我都不知道你要跑步
Teddy! I didn't know you were gonna run.
我也许只会跟着走一下
Oh, I'll probably walk.
我主要是想看看火鸡
I just wanted to see the turkeys.
我14岁时曾在火鸡农场工作过一个夏天
I worked on a turkey ranch one summer, when I was 14.
期间学到了很多人生真谛
I learned a lot about life.
以及关于火鸡粪便的知识
And a lot about turkey feces.
是个很有意义的夏天嘛  泰迪
Sounds like a magical summer, Teddy.
我们去玩游乐设施吧
Now let's hit the rides!
光站这里可玩不了大摆锤哦
We're not gonna get whiplash just standing here!
祝你好运  老妈
Good luck, Mom.
鲍勃在家做饭吗
Bob at home, cooking away?
没有  他今年拒绝参加感恩节活动
Nah. He's boycotting Thanksgiving this year.
-什么  -是的
- What? - Yeah.
但是鲍勃很喜欢感恩节
But Bob loves Thanksgiving.
我知道  由于我们
I know. He's mad
不愿一整天坐沙发上等着被喂食
that we all wanted to come here instead of sitting
想出来看看  鲍勃就生气了
around on the couch all day, waiting for food.
可怜的鲍勃  真可悲
Poor Bob. What a tragedy.
真正可悲的是我都来不及
Well, the real tragedy is that I don't have time
在活动开始前吃点玉米片
to get nachos before we start.
诶  也许还来得及
You know what? Maybe I do.
我提议我们从"翻滚蛋"开始
So, I say we start on the Scramble Pan
挨个往回玩  途径"狂暴山脉"
and work our way back through Violent Mountain
再到"碰碰大冒险"
and then the Bruise Cruise.
我看胳肢船也值得一玩
I wouldn't mind a trip on the Tickle Boat.
但吉恩  胳肢船已经不开了  记得吗
But, Gene, they closed it, remember?
有人坐那个丧命了
That guy died.
对哦
Oh, right.
-不过能这样死也值了  -是啊
- But what a way to go! - Yeah.
"翻滚蛋"我们来啦
Scramble Pan it is!
这样  很棒
This is... great?
不庆祝感恩节也不错嘛
Not celebrating Thanksgiving is kind of great.
我蛮喜欢  就我自己
I like it. I'm alone.
想干什么都成
I can do whatever I want.
我可以坐沙发上我不常坐的位置
I could sit in my not-usual spot on the couch.
还能翘二郎腿
I could even cross my legs,
再没人会取笑我
and no one would make fun of me.
-费力克斯  -在
- Felix? - Yes?
火鸡都喂过了吗
Have all the turkeys been fed?
不能再重演
We aren't going to have a repeat
不幸的咬手指事件了
of the unfortunate finger nibbling incident?
不会的  凯尔文  火鸡很好
No, Calvin. The turkeys are fine.
还有家鸡  和鸭
And the chickens. And the ducks.
-和鹅  -鹅
- And the geese. - "Geese"?
我不是让你找五百只火鸡吗  费力克斯
You were supposed to get 500 turkeys, Felix!
你只需要办这么一件事
You had one thing to do!
-就一件  -我试过了
- One! - I tried!
但火鸡供应现在很紧缺  也不知道为啥
Turkeys are scarce right now, for some reason!
这是什么原因
Oh, I wonder why that could be!
抱歉又让你失望了
Oh, I'm sorry I let you down again
我买了一批危险的火鸡...
by buying a bunch of dangerous birds that...
天哪
Oh, my God!
麦克风是开着的
The mic is on.
-大家好  -大家好
- Hi! - Oh, ho!
希望你们喜欢我们刚讲的
I hope you all enjoyed those Thanksgiving jokes
感恩节小笑话
we were just making.
感恩节的小幽默
A little light Thanksgiving humor.
我爱幽默  我非常爱笑
Oh, I love humor. I do love to laugh!
现在  我代表我哥凯尔文和我
Now, on behalf of myself and my brother Calvin,
欢迎各位来到首届
we'd like to welcome you all to the first annual
"超鸡棒"火鸡狂欢节
Turk-tacular Turkey Town Festival!
好耶
All right!
大家准备好
Is everybody ready
欢迎我们的活禽了吗
for some poultry in motion?
这声音听起来不太对啊
Those birds don't sound right.
嗨  中号鲁迪
Hey, Regular Sized Rudy.
看不出来你好这口啊
I didn't know you were a scramblin' man.
我一般不玩这个的  但我爸妈离婚了
I'm not usually, but since my parents are divorced,
今晚我得吃两顿
I gotta have two dinners,
所以我想把早饭吐出来
so I'm trying to make myself throw up breakfast.
我有一次也吃了两顿
One time I had two dinners
因为奥利吃不下他那份
because Ollie was too sick to eat his.
我那次得了疟疾
I had malaria!
别磨唧了  浪起来吧
Let's quit yakkin' and get crackin'!
米基  快  开始吧
Mickey, come on, let's do this!
火力开到最大
Set it to maximum!
没问题  用手扶着头
Okay, hold onto your heads like this
免得一会弄断了脖子
so your necks won't break!
现在让我们见证一项老少皆宜的
And now, the beginning of a new Thanksgiving tradition
感恩节新传统的诞生时刻
that's fun for the whole family.
-"火鸡快跑"...  -及其它
- The Running of the Turkeys... - etcetera.
各就各位  预备
On your mark... get set...
跑
go!
我去  我的天
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
琳达  快跑  快
Linda! Run! Run! Run!
不错  不错
Pretty good, pretty good.
现在换右腿在上
I'll try right over left now.
也不错
Also good.
我擦  鸡  有鸡
Oh, ah, no! Birds! Birds! Birds! Birds!
不好意思  借过  让一让
Excuse me! Excuse me! Make way, make way! Sorry. Hey...
让一让  借过一下
Coming through! Here we go, pardon us.
怎么  怎么回事
What...? What happened?
我变矮变扭曲了
I'm short and wiggly!
又变高变扭曲了
I'm tall and wiggly.
原来是哈哈镜
it's a fun mirror.
哈哈镜
It's a fun mirror.
琳达
Linda!
琳达  是我  泰迪
Linda, it's me, Teddy!
跟你一个镇的
From your town!
泰迪  发生什么了
Teddy? Wha-What's going on, Teddy?
我怎么来这里的
How did I get in here?
那些鸡冲上来时  大多数人都跑了
When the birds attacked, most people got away,
但你被这只独眼火鸡
but you got knocked out
给撞晕了
by this freaky one-eyed cyclops turkey.
然后我把你弄到这里来了
So I picked you up and carried you here.
我昏迷多久了
How long have I been out?
一切都变了
A lot's changed.
我们暂时还不用为增加人口而繁衍后代
We don't have to start repopulating the Earth yet,
但那一天终会到来
but eventually we might have to do just that.
-不知道  -泰迪
- I don't know... - Teddy!
我在这里多久了
How long have I been in here?
五六分钟吧
Five, maybe six minutes.
我的天  孩子们
Oh, my God, the kids!
我小孩呢
Where are the kids?!
我是素食主义者
But I'm a vegan!
米基竟然就这么不管我们了
I can't believe Mickey left us here!
这些鸡越逼越近了
Those birds are getting awfully close.
但愿它们没买坐这个的票
I hope they don't have tickets for this ride!
我们得下去
We got to get off this thing.
安迪  奥利  看来你们得
Andy, Ollie, you seem like you're up for a challenge
肩负起这个艰巨任务  跳下去关掉它了
of getting off the ride and shutting it down.
我们什么都愿意试
We'll try anything.
是的  我都在我阿姨家里尝了虾
Yeah! I tried shrimp at my aunt's house!
挺好  去关吧
Great. Go get 'em!
发生了什么
Oh, what happened?
我们穿越了
We travelled through time!
看来得我出马了
I guess I'll give it a whirl. Literally.
欢迎回来
Hey. Welcome back.
我们出生时也是在蛋[卵子]里转来转去
We're gonna die like we were born.
这下得怎么来怎么走了
Spinning around in an egg!
看来你感触颇深
That really makes you think.
挺好
This is great.
终于不用一直给火鸡抹油了
Don't have to keep getting up to baste.
不用抹油  不想抹油
Baste not, want not.
听懂了吗  听懂了
You get it? Yes.
我不用抹油[捣毁巴士底狱]了
I don't have to storm the Baste-ille.
听懂了吗
Get it?
大概吧
Kind of.
巴士底狱是法国一所监狱
It was a prison in France.
巴士底  我说"抹油"
The Bastille, and I said "Baste-ille."
现在是从码头发回的直播报道
I'm here live at the wharf
今天这里的火鸡快跑变成了一场恐怖事件
where today's Turkey Trot turned into turkey terror.
到底发生了什么
What exactly happened in there today?
其实没那么糟糕  真的
I assure you it wasn't that bad, really.
人们的反应有些夸张了  就这样
I mean, people overreacted, that's all.
那些鸡都疯了
Those birds went crazy, man!
它们想弄死我们
They tried to kill us!
这人明显已经疯了
That man is clearly insane.
看他的衣服就知道了
You saw his outfit!
所以你关了大门  把鸡关在里面了
So, you closed the gates to keep the birds in?
没错  它们的翅膀被剪过了
That's right. Their wings are clipped.
也就是说它们是出不来的
That means that they're contained.
那人呢
But what about the people?
还有人在里面吗
Was anyone left inside?
没有  要有可就是我们的公关危机了
No, that would be a PR nightmare.
今天不会发生这种事
Which we are not having today.
不会  谢谢您呐
No, thank you.
今天完全可以说是大获成功
No, today was nothing less than a total success.
-你的头条搞定了  -没错
- There's your headline! - Yes.
快记下来
Write that down.
这是直播
We're on live television.
那就打个字幕
Then make it into a graphic.
要旋转着插入屏幕的那种
A fun one that spins in.
大获成功
Total success!
-对  -我们会处理的
- Yeah. - We'll get right on that.
还比较顺利
Okay. Well, that went well.
我也这么觉得
Yes. I think it did, too.
我们回去吃饭吧
Should we go home for dinner?
-好啊  我快饿死了  -是啊
- Yes, I am starving. - Yeah.
那啥  确定所有人都出来了吗
Did everyone get out, by the way?
不确定
No. No, no.
我关门的时候还有人在尖叫
I mean, they were screaming when I closed the gates,
所以应该不是所有人都出来了
so I don't think so.
但谁会相信他们呢
But who's gonna believe them, right?
还在录呢
we're still recording!
-唉呀妈呀  -看啊
- Oh, dear Lord! - Well, look at that.
是  这是今天第二次了
Yep. Happened twice now.
看呐
Look at 'em.
它们都是从哪儿来的  家禽监狱吗
Where'd they come from, poultry prison?
不妙
Yeah, this is bad.
它们的啄序全打乱了
Their pecking order's all messed up.
啄序  指鸡群中存在的等级  最高级的
可以啄次一级的而不被还击  次一级的可以啄再次一级
啥  啄序
What? "Pecking order"?
你在说什么呢
What are you talking about?
每个火鸡群都有一只火鸡
Every turkey group has one guy
能啄所有火鸡  而等级位于他之下的
who can peck everyone, then the guy below him
可以啄除了他上级以外的所有火鸡
who can peck everyone except for the top guy,
以此类推  最后是那谁都不能啄的倒霉蛋
and so on until the sad sack who can't peck anyone.
真恶劣
Oh, that's terrible.
简直和《观点》脱口秀里的女人们一样
It's like the ladies on The View.
美国一档脱口秀节目  节目形式为
四位女主持人就时事新闻发表各自观点
现在这样人鸡混杂
Yeah, with all these bird sand people mixed in,
把他们都搞糊涂了
they don't know what to do.
他们现在见啥啄啥  一团混乱
They're pecking everything! It's chaos!
我们还是得去找孩子们
Well, we still got to go find the kids.
我们悄悄潜出去  准备好了吗
Let's just tiptoe past them. Ready?
好了
Ready.
跑啊
Run!
就是它  独眼怪[希腊神话人物]
It's him, Cyclops!
之前把你放倒的就是它
That's the one who knocked you down earlier.
天哪  它真是恨我
Oh, God, he hates me!
天哪
Oh, my God!
-我知道怎么回事了  -什么
- I know what's happening! - What?
我们抛弃了感恩节
We rejected Thanksgiving
它现在来报复了
and now it's attacking us!
什么话  琳
That's crazy, Lin,
这些火鸡只是因为和其它禽类
these turkeys are just all mixed up.
关在一起而产生混乱了
They were keeping them with other birds.
这是动物本性  不是《女巫也疯狂》
It's biology, not hocus pocus.
迪士尼于1993年推出的魔法冒险电影
我好爱那部电影
I love that movie!
我们要怎么找孩子们呢
How are we ever gonna find the kids?
他们在"翻滚蛋"那边
They're on the Scramble Pan.
天哪  火鸡都会说话了
Oh, my God! The birds have learned to talk!
不  不
No, no!
-是我  米基  -米基  米基吗
- It's me, Mickey. - Mickey? Mickey?!
孩子们在"翻滚蛋"那边吗
The kids are on the Scramble Pan?
什么  我听不太清
What? I-I can't hear you.
-我说  -打开你的麦克风
- I said the... - Turn on your microphone.
-什么  -给
- What? - Here.
我的宝贝们在"翻滚蛋"那边吗
My kids are on the Scramble Pan?
是的  我看见他们了
Yeah, I, uh, saw them.
我把他们丢那儿
As I was leaving them there,
然后跑这儿来躲着了
and, uh, running over here to hide.
你就这样不顾他们死活了吗
You abandoned my kids?
算是吧
Sort of.
但其实他们在游乐设施里更安全
But, uh, you know, they're safer on the ride,
你仔细想想的话
so I kind of did the right thing,
我也算做件大好事
if-if you think about it!
天哪
Oh, man.
人吃动物的日子要结束了
You can only eat an animal for so long.
火鸡要开始统治地球了
It's the turkeys time to rule the Earth now.
人类本有机会的但我们搞砸了
We had our chance and we blew it.
不 是火鸡的啄序被打乱了
No, it's the pecking order!
是感恩节神灵发怒了
It's the spirit of Thanksgiving!
-这说法太荒谬了  -别说我荒谬
- That's crazy talk! - Don't call me crazy.
这说法不荒谬
That's not crazy talk.
各位  各位  各位  各位
Guys, guys, guys, guys!
-我没说你荒谬  -我们别吵了
- I didn't say you were crazy. - We got to stop fighting!
我们开始内讧了
We're turning on each other.
这就是他们的目的
This is exactly what they want!
我们得去找孩子们  米基
We gotta get the kids, Mickey.
你和我们一起
You gotta come with us.
我们需要你帮忙关游乐设施
We need your help to turn off the ride.
我很乐意帮忙  琳达
I would love to do that, Linda.
但我藏在这些毛绒玩具里
But I'm actually really comfortable here,
真挺舒服的
hiding in these stuffed animals.
他们给我安全感  对不住了
I just feel safe with these guys, I'm sorry.
看着是挺舒服的
That looks nice.
我忽然有个点子
That gives me an idea!
米基  我们要过来了
Mickey, we're coming over!
嗨  白日威士忌
Hey, daytime whiskey.
来看看我的CD收藏吧
Want to meet my CD collection?
我感觉你们会合得来的
I feel like you guys would hit it off.
唐娜・莎曼
Donna Summer?
唐娜・莎曼: 美国七十年代著名流行乐女歌手
莎曼时间来啦
It's Summer time.
*调暗灯光  亲爱的*
*Dim all the lights, sweet darling*
唐娜・莎曼演唱歌曲《调暗灯光》
*今晚我们将共度漫漫长夜*
*'Cause tonight it's all the way *
*嘿  宝贝*
*Hey, baby *
*打开老式留声机*
*Turn up the old Victrola*
*与我共舞今宵*
*Gonna dance the night away...*
吉恩  蒂娜  露易丝
Gene, Tina, Louise!
等下  那是咱妈吗
Hey, wait, is that Mom?
是的  她先喊的我的名字
Yes! She said my name first!
老妈  救命
Mom! Help!
-快  米基  关了它  -马上
- All right, Mickey, turn it off. - Can do.
哎呀  我把钥匙扔海里了
Oh, shoot. I threw the key into the ocean.
-什么  -我怕让那些火鸡抢了去
- You what? - I didn't want the birds to get it.
我们可不能让高科技落入火鸡之手
We can't let this technology fall into their hands.
还有别的办法可以关掉它吗
Is there another way to turn it off?
等下  那有个操作员醉酒紧急开关
Wait! There's a drunk operator override switch on the ride!
-什么  -这儿所有的游乐设施都有
- What?! - All the rides in the park have them.
以防一旦操作人员喝多了跑去玩游乐设施
In case the operator gets drunk and goes on the ride,
就没人能关掉它了
leaving no one to turn it off.
想得很周到嘛
Oh, smart.
好吧  我来了
Okay, here I go.
就像停自行车一样
Just like turning off a bicycle.
天哪  我要吐了
Oh, God, I'm gonna barf.
各位  让我来
Guys, I can do this.
天哪
Oh, God.
好晕
So dizzy.
天哪  这真惨
Oh, God, this is bad.
真恶心
So nauseous!
真的假的
Seriously?!
我们在这玩意上转了一个小时了
We've been on this thing for a freaking hour,
没一个人吐  吉恩还吃了包零食
and no one's barfed. Gene even had a snack.
还得老妈来
Looks like it's up to Mama.
我滴神啊  小孩玩这个不可能安全的
Holy moly, this thing cannot be safe for children.
你们这些大人玩的还蛮好的嘛
But you adults seem to be doing really well with it!
我要有什么东西能扔到开关上就好了
If only I had something to throw at the switch.
天哪
Oh, my God.
我的水宝宝
My water babies.
永别了  小瓶瓶
Good-bye, baby bottle.
小凯伦
Little Karen.
没关系
Okay, no problem.
我  我还有九个
I-I got nine more.
最后一发了
Okay, this is the last one.
小蒂米  我一直最喜欢你了
Little Timmy, you were always my favorite.
能换个人扔不
Please let someone else do it.
我可以的
I can do it!
-好耶  -厉害
- Yay! - Nice!
干得好  鲁迪
Way to go, Rudy!
正常的鲁迪  没犯哮...
Rudy-- one, asthma-- zer...
你们还好吗  宝贝们
Are you okay, my babies?
还好  不过我以后可能都要
Yep, I'm probably always gonna move
像这样转着圈走路了
in little circles like this, though.
看来我们有伴了
Looks like we've got company.
坏伙伴
Bad company.
这可不是什么乐队的名字
And not the band!
应该不是吧
Probably.
动物控制中心
大家冷静  我们来了
Everyone relax, we're here.
那些火鸡疯了
Those birds are crazy.
看我的警棍被弄的
Look what one of them did to my nightstick.
请靠边
Please step aside.
我们来处理
Let us take care of this, all right?
谁来控制
Who's in control?
动物管制中心
Animal Control!
开门
Open 'em up!
*宝贝*
*Oh, baby*
*打开老式留声机*
*Turn on that old Victrola*
*与我共舞今宵  多美丽*
*Gonna dance the night-- it's so bright *
跳起来
Okay, here we go!
天呐  我们被包围了
Oh, god, we're surrounded.
谁能帮我打下过敏针
Who wants to be in charge of my epi-pen?
我对鹅和鸭子过敏
I'm allergic to geese and ducks!
那我就不邀请你来参加我的鸭鸭鹅派对了
I will not invite you to my duck-duck-goose party, then.
理解
Understood.
泰迪  你干嘛呢
Teddy, what are you doing?
我在哄火鸡
I'm whooping and hollering.
我在农场打工的时候
This is how I used to get the turkeys
就是这么让火鸡跟我走的
to follow me on the farm.
你们要活下去
Save yourselves.
向我的过去致敬吧  琳达
Honor my memory, Linda!
-记住我的名字  -泰迪
- Remember my name! - Teddy!
别阻止我  露易丝
Don't try to stop me, Louise.
我刚想起你的名字  你叫泰迪
I just remembered your name, it's Teddy!
没错
Right.
我永远不会忘记他那惊人的腿
I'll never forget his incredible legs.
像热狗一样的腿
They looked like hotdogs.
我们得到前门去
We have to get to the front gate.
这会儿救援应该到了
Help must be there by now.
跳得真棒  鲍勃
Great dancing, Bob.
该奖励自己些啤酒了
Time to reward myself with some beer.
嗨  火鸡滴油管
Oh, hello, uh, turkey baster.
你还好吗
How-how-how are you?
好  很好
Good, good.
那就好
Uh, yeah, good.
我挺好的  真的
I-I-I'm doing really good.
是啊
Yeah.
好神奇  我刚刚
That's funny, I was just, uh...
我刚刚  还提到你来着
I was, I was... just talking about you.
见到你很高兴
It was good to see you.
我得去...
I-I should get back to...
没错  真是
Yeah, it was...
很高兴见到你
It was nice to see you.
你看起来挺好的
You look great.
怎么了  我  我
What? I-I...
我看到你了  好吗
I-I-I see you, okay?
你已经表达你的立场了
You-You've made your point.
好吧
Fine.
这就是你想要的吗
Is this what you want?
你现在开心了吗
A-Are you happy now?
是吗  是吗  这样满意了
Yeah, yeah? That good?
你想出来是吗
Do you want it to come out?
你现在就想出来吗
You want to do this right now?
立刻马上出来吗
真是  真是太像你的作风了
That's a cl... that's classic.
太像你的作风了  滴油管
That's classic you, turkey baster!
太像你了
Classic you.
不愿呆在抽屉里
Not fitting in the drawer.
执意不从
Deliberately not!
好极了
That's great.
得了吧
Oh, come on.
滴油管  别这样看着我
don't look at me like that, turkey baster.
别这样看着我
Don't look at me like that.
我  我也不想的
I... I didn't want this!
你觉得我愿意这样
You think I wanted this?!
我也不想
But I didn't!
我不想的
I didn't.
我也不想这样
This isn't what I wanted.
我从来没想过和你分开
I-I never wanted to be apart from you.
之前那些都是在演戏
It was all an act.
是  是个谎言
It was... it was a lie.
天呐
Oh, god.
好多鼻涕
That's so much snot.
你知道吗
You know what?
我要做晚饭
I'm gonna do it.
你是对的  滴油管
You're right, turkey baster.
我可是鲍勃
I'm Bob.
我是个厨子
I make dinner.
现在还不迟
It's not too late.
杂货店还有一个小时才关门
The grocery store's open for another hour.
我们还来得及
We can still do this!
开始吧  咱们走
Let's go! Let's go!
起来
Get up!
起  我起不来
Get... I can't get...
天呐
Oh, my God!
我
I...
快起来  醉汉
Let's get up, drunk!
我好晕
I am dizzy!
我真的好晕
I'm really dizzy.
天呐
Oh, my God.
我得坐下来
I gotta sit down.
给我们  给我们一分钟
Give us... give us a minute.
请呆在室内
Please remain indoors.
重复一遍  家禽暴动
I repeat, there's been a poultry-based disturbance.
请呆在室内
Please remain indoors.
家禽
Poultry!
不是吧
Oh, come on!
大家都到这后面来
Everyone, get behind there.
一个人都没有
There's no one here.
没人来救我们
No one came for us.
没人在意
No one even cared.
我们都会死在这儿的
We're all gonna die here.
我们都要死了
We're all gonna die.
对不起  对不起  谢谢
I'm sorry, I'm sorry. Thank you.
我决定加入那些火鸡了
Well, I've decided to go join the birds.
我本来也爱吃面包
I eat lots of bread already,
我不想再抵抗了
and I'm tired of fighting.
再见
Good-bye.
我会想你的  不过我理解
I'll miss you, but I understand.
那是什么
What is that?
我听过这个声音
I know that sound.
等等
Wait a minute...
不可能
It can't be.
没错
It is.
是胳肢船
The old Tickle Boat.
你们有没有觉得浑身发痒
I hope you guys aren't ticklish.
船来了哦  胳肢船来啦
Because of the boat... Tickle Boat.
小婊砸
Son of a bitch.
我一路上都在想这段台词
I was thinking of that line the whole way here.
还不错  是吧
Pretty good, right?
挺好的
Pretty good.
我们能上来么
Hey, can we get in?
我们回来了  鲍鲍
We're coming, Bobby.
"去下商店  马上回来
"Went to store real quick.
爱你的  鲍勃"
Love forever, Bob."
这真是一张完美的便条
That's a perfectly good note.
一点看不出喝醉的样子
That doesn't sound drunk at all.
快到了
We're almost there.
瞧瞧  我在给这些火鸡竖中指
Hey, look-- I'm giving those birds the bird.
老妈  老妈  我们也能比么
Mom, Mom, can we do it, too?
好吧  仅限今天  因为今天过节
Yes. Just today, 'cause it's a holiday.
像这样
Like this.
往上  往上  高点  高点
Up, up, higher, higher.
我感觉到了
Oh, I feel it.
杀伤力好大
It's so insulting.
所以下不为例哦
Never do that again.
锁&钥匙商店
蛮有趣的嘛  就我们俩
This is fun, the two of us.
我们应该常出来散步
We should go on more walks.
感恩节快乐  朋友
Happy Thanksgiving... friendly guy.
省又多超市
看路
Hey, careful.
那老兄喝醉了吧
I think that guy was drunk.
有人吗
Hello?
好奇怪
That's weird.
好吧  去采购晚餐食材了
Okay, just gotta grab every single thing for dinner.
没问题
That's no problem.
拜  安迪  拜  奥利
Bye, Andy. Bye, Ollie.
感恩节快乐
Happy Thanksgiving.
快回去  快快快快
Go, go, go, go, go!
谢谢你救了奥利的命
I'm thankful that you saved Ollie's life.
谢谢你救了安迪的命
I'm thankful you saved Andy's life.
我们回家吧
Now, get out of here!
鲍勃  鲍鲍  我们回来了
Bob? Bobby, we're home!
对不起
We're sorry!
我们没想在这么重要的日子
We didn't mean to leave you all alone
-留你一个...  -老爸
- on such a big... - Dad?
你在玩捉迷藏吗  有意思
If you're hiding, that's fun.
他没有
He's not hiding.
他去买火鸡了
Giblets.
我们去超市找你们老爸
We're going to get Daddy at the store.
鲁迪宝贝儿  你确定不要我们
Rudy, honey, are you sure you don't want us
把你送回家吗
to drop you off at home?
我和你们一起去
I'm going with you.
我还挺好奇最后结局的
I kind of want to see how this one ends.
亲爱的鲁迪
Oh, sweet Rudy.
我看你大概撑不到那时候了
You probably won't live to see the end.
你在这儿呢
There you are.
今年差点就放过你了
The one that almost got away.
你好
Hello.
你是一只活火鸡
You're an actual turkey.
站在我面前
That's standing there.
还只有一只眼睛
And you have only one eye.
不是说那不好
Not that that's bad.
我手上这兄弟在我找到他之前就是这样了
He-he was like this when I found him.
因为这里是超市嘛
'Cause it's a grocery store.
你  你在这儿干嘛
W-What are you doing here?
都跟在我后面
Okay, everyone follow me.
-老爸  -跑  快跑
- Dad! - Run! Run!
天呐  是独眼怪
Oh, my God, it's Cyclops!
这到底是咋了
What the hell is happening?!
我们没听你的
We didn't do Thanksgiving right,
没好好过感恩节
and we didn't listen to you,
现在感恩节来报复我们了
and now Thanksgiving's attacking us!
有道理
That makes sense.
不是  这是火鸡的本能
No, it's biological!
不对  这是一次火鸡革命  鲍勃
No it's the beginning of a turkey revolution, Bob.
我们得赶紧站好队
We got to pick sides.
他啄我了
He pecked me!
我去  好痛
Holy crap, that hurts.
天
Oh, God.
互啄终极对决来了
The final "Peckoning."
互啄
Pecked!
对了  互啄
That's it-- pecked.
泰迪好像说对了
I think Teddy was right!
-是吗  -我知道怎么做了
- I was? - And I know what to do.
-是吗  -泰迪说对了
- You do? - Teddy was right?!
琳  你这是干嘛
Lin, what are you doing?!
我要成为火鸡啄序里地位最高的那个
I'm getting to the top of the pecking order.
琳达  你真是天才
Linda, you're a genius.
对吧
Right?
我去  他妈的痛死了
Damn it. Son of a bitch.
真的有用吗
Did that actually work?
退后  我们来检验一下
Stand back, let's see.
我成火鸡之首啦
I'm the alpha turkey.
是的  我猜对了
Yeah, that's what I thought.
你们自己互塞去吧
Go stuff each other.
向胳肢船前进
To the Tickle Boat!
等下  是那艘出过人命的胳肢船吗
Wait, the Tickle Boat that killed that guy?
是的
Yeah.
我们走  快快快快
Let's go. Go, go, go, go.
-快走  -好吧
- Come on, go. - All right.
动起来  快出去  快快快
Move, move, move, out, out, go, go, go.
各位
Well, everyone,
我敬我们大家
here's to us.
今天一天我们经历了太多...
We've been through so much in the last...
等下  别说了  等等
Wait, stop, wait, wait.
我想说
I want to say:
敬鲍勃  感恩节是他最爱的日子
Here is to Bob on his favorite day.
鲍勃  敬你
Bob! Yes!
敬鲍勃
Bob...!
-谢谢  -好耶
- Thank you. - Yes!
我要敬火鸡女王琳达
And here's to Linda, queen of the turkeys.
他啄起人来真有一套
She really knows how to peck people.
是的是的
Hear, hear.
敬啄人女王
Queen of the Peckers.
真好
Nice.
说到火鸡
And speaking of turkey--
谁想来点啊
who wants some?
不是吧  没人想吃火鸡
Wait, no one wants turkey?
-不太想  -我觉得不太好
- Not so much. - I just don't think it's appropriate.
再也不想吃了
Probably never ever again.
我还能闻到活火鸡的气味呢  鲍勃
I can still smell 'em, Bob.
就在我内心的鼻腔里
They're inside my mind nose.
-我去做意面  -好耶
- I'll make spaghetti. - Yeah!
我不能吃意面  但我可以喝碗意面汁
I can't have pasta, but I'll eat a bowl of sauce.
那我给你做意面汁
I'll make sauce.
好吧  但我要放唐娜・莎曼的歌
Fine, I'm putting on Donna Summer, though.
唐娜・莎曼
Who's Donna Summer?
鲁迪  你会爱死她的
Oh, Rudy, you are gonna love her.
费力克斯  我们开始玩许愿骨吧
Well, Felix, should we do the wishbone?
好的  我们开始...
Yes, I guess we shou...
-那是什么  -啥
- What was that? - What was what?
快来玩许愿骨  快  快来
Come do the wishbone. Come, come on.
不不不  我听到外面有什么声音
No, no, no. I heard something outside.
你没听到吗  那是什么
You didn't hear that? What was that?
快来  我希望你能过来玩许愿骨
Come... I wish you would come do the wishbone.
好吧
All right...
看来只能我赢了
I guess I win.
*我的人生*
*There's been a change *
唐娜・莎曼歌曲《爱已被我控制》
"Love is in Control"
*有了变化*
*Inside my life *
*我只想让你知道*
*And I just wanna let you know *
*我的手指已扣住扳机*
*I've got my finger on the trigger *
*爱已被我控制*
*Love is in control *
*我的手指已扣住扳机*
*I've got my finger on the trigger *
*我不会放手*
*I ain't lettin' go*
*妈妈曾教导我*
*Mama used to tell me *
*姑娘  最好给你的枪上好膛*
*Girl, you better load your gun up right *
*她说  你要让枪口冒烟*
*She said, "You, you gotta come out smokin' *
*每次出击都竭尽全力*
*Hit it with your best shot every time... *